James R. "Jim" Dunnam papers, Inclusive: 1982-2011, Bulk: 1996-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
James R. "Jim" Dunnam papers
Inclusive: 1982-2011, Bulk: 1996-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
99
Dunnam, Jim, 1963 -
73 document boxes and 9 oversized boxes
The James R. "Jim" Dunnam papers represent the Texas congressional career of Jim Dunnam, spanning the 75th through the 81st Texas Legislatures. Records include correspondence, legislation, administrative files, and audio-visual materials among other items.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
James R. “Jim” Dunnam served as the Texas State Representative for District 57 from 1997-2011. He was born December 12, 1963, in Waco, Texas, where he continues to reside. Dunnam attended Baylor University where he attained his BBA in 1986 and JD from Baylor Law School in 1987. He began working as a member of his family’s law practice, Dunnam & Dunnam, L.L.P. in 1988.
Dunnam ran as the Democratic candidate in the 1996 election, won, and served until losing his bid for re-election in November 2010. Considered a leader in the Democratic Party, he was named the leader of the House Democratic Caucus from 2003-2011. Dunnam’s major bills included charter-school reform and restrictions on open containers of alcohol in cars. Additionally, he worked to improve public schools, economic development, affordable health care, focused on the Bosque River, higher education, and oversaw the evaluation and re-authorization of the State Bar of Texas and the State Board of Law Examiners. In 2003, he led the controversial Killer Ds walkout to Ardmore, Oklahoma to stall Republican Tom DeLay’s mid-decade redistricting plan.
Dunnam was appointed to several committees and acquired numerous awards. He served on the Texas Supreme Court Rules Advisory Committee, 1998-2003, Texas Sunset Advisory Committee, 2001-2005, House Select Committee on Judicial Interpretation of Law, and the House Committee for Oversight of Family Law and Texas Family Code. He served as Chair of the Interim Committee on Charter Schools, the Select Committee on Federal Economic Stabilization Funding, and as Vice-Chair of the Committee on Criminal Jurisprudence. Dunnam was named Baylor’s Young Lawyer of the Year in 2001, and one of Texas’s Ten Best Legislators in 2001 by Texas Monthly and in 2005 by Capitol Inside. He is certified as a civil trial law and family law attorney.
Scope and Content
The Jim Dunnam papers cover an expanse of 1982-2011, though the bulk of the papers are from 1997-2011. These years span the 75th through the 81st Texas Legislatures. Materials document Dunnam’s service as a Texas Representative during these sessions. The papers cover a wide variety of topics pertinent to Texas House District 57 during this time, including the Bosque River, charter schools, education, health, lawsuit reform, redistricting, school finance, Supreme Court of Texas, taxes, the Texas Youth Commission, and tort reform. There is a significant amount of material related to the Killer Ds walkout to Ardmore, Oklahoma, led by Representative Dunnam, and a variety of unique campaign material items.
Each of these topics present themselves in various formats throughout the collection. Series I, Administrative, consists of office paperwork related to everyday functions, appointments, travel, campaigns, and biographical material. Series II, Correspondence, covers a wide array of topics, as well as McLennan County-specific letters and correspondence between members of the legislature. Series III, Constituents, refers to materials on cities and counties within District 57, phone logs, questionnaires on education funding, reading files, Dunnam’s speeches, and thank you notes. Series IV, Legislative, is the largest series and is organized by subseries representing each session of the Legislature in which Dunnam participated. Each of these subseries contain sub-subseries, including House Bills, Senate Bills, Joint Resolutions, Commemoratives and Commendations, and Topical. Series V, Newspapers, includes copied clippings about Dunnam, the Texas Legislature, politics, and the state. Series VI, Personal, holds material about the Texas/Oklahoma Bar Grievance, and Series VII, Press Releases, contains topical material. Series VIII, Audio-Visual, is the last series, and includes four types of media: cassettes, CDs, photographs, and VHS tapes.
Arrangement
The Jim Dunnam papers are arranged in eight series by format and topic, and often alphabetically or chronologically within those series. They are the following: I. Administrative, II. Correspondence, III. Constituents, IV. Legislative, V. Newspapers, VI. Personal, VII. Press Releases, VIII. Audio-Visual. Several of these series contain subseries, and some sub-subseries.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 99. Acquired 2013-01-01
Related Resources
Related references
“Jim Dunnam.” Dunnam & Dunnam: Attorneys at Law. Accessed March 17, 2017.
“Jim Dunnam.” Legal Directories. 2017.
“Jim Dunnam’s Biography.” Vote Smart. Accessed March 17, 2017.
Jim Dunnam papers, Accession #99, Baylor Collections of Political Materials, W. R. Poage Legislative Library, Baylor University.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Dunnam, Jim -- Correspondence.; Dunnam, Jim, 1963- -- Archives.; Dunnam, Jim.
Subjects (Organizations)
Democratic Party (Tex.); Texas. Legislature. House of Representatives.; Texas. Supreme Court.
Places
Bosque River (Tex.); McLennan County (Tex.) -- Politics and government.
Subjects
Apportionment (Election law) -- Texas.; Charter schools -- Law and legislation -- Texas.; Educational law and legislation -- Texas.; Legislators -- Texas -- Archives.; Political campaigns -- Texas -- McLennan County.; Public health laws -- Texas.; Torts -- Texas.
Genres
Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Legislative materials.; Photographs.; Questionnaires.; Records (Documents); Speeches.
- Administrative, 1992-2011; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  This series includes Dunnam’s administrative papers from his full tenure in office. It contains five subseries: General, Appointment Schedules, Campaign Materials, Personal, and Travel Vouchers. The General subseries contains items such as Dunnam’s desk nameplate, guestbooks, and various office records. The Campaign Materials include invitations, finance reports, and campaign ads and objects. Awards, memberships, and biographical material are included in the Personal subseries. This series is in good condition.
  - General, 1996-2011; 1
    - Computers, 1999-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Desk Nameplate, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - District Office Lease, 1997-2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - District Office Lease, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - First Session, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Honorary Page and Group Tours Program, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Honorary Page and Group Tours Program, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - House Committees, Numerical Analysis, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - House District 57 Zip Codes, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Incumbent Residence Locations, 2005 January (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Inventory, 1999-2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Invoice, House Democratic Campaign Caucus, 2004 December (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Invoices, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Lease Agreement for Waco 2010 La Salle, 1999 April (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Legislative Handbook Request, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Mexican-American Legislative Caucus, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Newly — Elected Representative Information Packet, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Office Closing Procedures and Record Retention Schedule, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Office Equipment, 1998 October (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Order Forms, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Parking, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Postage Stamps, 1998 July-October (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Private Phone Line, 1997 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Reception Guestbook, 2003 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Records, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Speaker of the House Pledges, 2002 November (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Staff, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Stationery, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - State Property Verification, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Texas Commission on Human Rights Complaint, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Transmittal of State Records, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - TXDOT Registration Renewal, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - TXDOT State Official Plates, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Unopposed Democratic Candidates, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Visitor’s Register, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Appointment Schedules, 1997-2010; 2
    - General (1 of 3), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - General (2 of 3), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - General (3 of 3), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - General, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - General, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - General, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - General, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - General, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - General, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - General, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - General, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - General, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - General, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - General, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - General, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - General, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - LeeAnn and Michelle, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Texas Suite Hospitality Schedule, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Campaign Materials, 1992-2010; 3
    - 79th Texas Legislature Swearing-In Ceremony Program and Invitation, 2005 January 11 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 2004 Democratic State Convention Program, 2004 June 17-19 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Anti- Tony Sanchez, circa 2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Bert Vandiver Invitation, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Campaign Contributions 2006, 2006 April (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Campaign Contributions 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Campaign Finance Report, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Campaign Finance Report, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Campaign Finance Report, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Treasurer, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Chet Edwards Bar-B-Que Invitation, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Chet Edwards Re-election Victory Party Invitation, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Chet Edwards Wine and Cheese Invitation, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Clinton and Gore Campaign Button, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Dan Ellis Campaign Letter, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Convention Kraft Macaroni and Cheese Box, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Dunnam Campaign Pamphlet, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Dunnam Campaign Stickers and Button, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Dunnam Opponent’s Campaign Ads, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - “The Dunnam Report”, 2002 October (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Election Maps by Ethnicity, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Funds, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Holt Getterman Campaign, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Invitation to Campaign Kickoff Party 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Invitation to Campaign Kickoff Party 2004 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Invitation to Jim Dunnam Swearing-In Ceremony, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Invitation to 77th Texas Legislature Send-Off Party, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Jeffrey Hibbs Website Info, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Jim Dunnam Campaign Ads, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Jim Dunnam Invitations CD, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Jim Dunnam Re-Election Campaign Postcards, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Jim Dunnam Re-Election Campaign Reception Invitation, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Jim Dunnam Report, 2003 May (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Jim Dunnam State Representative District 57 Oversized Magnet, undated (Box OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Jim Meyer Campaign, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - John Mabry Campaign, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Join the Libertarian Party Oversized Magnet, undated (Box OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Keep Jim Dunnam T-Shirt (1 of 3), undated (Box 81 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Keep Jim Dunnam T-Shirt (2 of 3), undated (Box 81 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Keep Jim Dunnam T-Shirt (3 of 3), undated (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Kip Averitt Campaign, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - The Libertarian Party of Texas Oversized Magnet, undated (Box OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Margaret Mirabal Campaign, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Opposition, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Political Action Committees (PAC), March-Primary Elections, 2000 February (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Polling Places, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Re-Elect Jim Dunnam Poster, undated (Box OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Russell Devorsky Campaign Finance Report, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Speaker of the House Support, circa 2005 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Stationery, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Tony Sanchez Ad, circa 2001 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Vote Jim Dunnam Nail Files, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Voter Registration Public Information Request, 2010 October 26 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Voter Contact Plan, 2010 May 19 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Walt Fair Campaign, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Yard Signs, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Personal, 1996-2003; 4
    - General, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Awards, 1997-2002 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Biography, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Dunnam and Dunnam, L.L.P., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Flemming Fellows Leadership Institute (1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Flemming Fellows Leadership Institute (2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Memberships, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Recreational Activity, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Supreme Court of the United States, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Waco-McLennan County Bar Association Directory, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Travel Vouchers, 1997-2001; 5
    - General, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - General, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - General, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - General, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Blank Travel Forms, 2000, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1990-2010; 2
  This series contains correspondence with the following subseries: General, McLennan County, and Members. The General subseries is organized topically and includes issues such as education, health, lawsuit reform, redistricting, and taxes. The McLennan County subseries covers correspondence pertaining to the county, arranged chronologically, and the Members subseries refers to members of Texas Legislature, also arranged chronologically. Additionally, the Members subseries includes correspondence on redistricting. The Correspondence series is in good condition.
  - General, 1996-2010; 1
    - General (1 of 3), 1997-2004 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - General (2 of 3), 1997-2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - General (3 of 3), 1997-2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - General, 2003-2009 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Abortion, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Accounting, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - African American History, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Airplanes, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Alamo, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Alcohol and Drugs, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - American Archaeology Group Lawsuit, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Animals, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Animals, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Annexation, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Appointments, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Auto Insurance, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Big Brothers/Big Sisters, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Birthdays, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Board Members, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Budget, 1997-2003 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Builders Association, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Campaign, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Capitol Tours (1 of 2), 1997-2007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Capitol Tours (2 of 2), 1997-2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Cemeteries, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Charity, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Charity, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Checks, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Child Care, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cigarettes and Tobacco, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Community Affairs, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Condolences, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Congratulations (1 of 2), 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Congratulations (2 of 2), 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Congratulations, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Conservation, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Construction, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Contractors, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Council for the Humanities, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Courts, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Credit Union, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Criminal Justice, 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Criminal Justice, 2003-2007 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Death Penalty, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Defense, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Democrats, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Development, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Drag Race, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Eagle Scouts, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Economic Development, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Education, American Sign Language, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Education, Athletics, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Education, Boy’s/Girl’s State, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Education, Charter Schools, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Education, Dropouts, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Education, Educational Technology, 1997-2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Education, Higher Education (1 of 3), 1997-2001 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Education, Higher Education (2 of 3), 1997-2001 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Education, Higher Education (3 of 3), 1997-2001 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Education, Higher Education, 2000-2006 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Education, Prekindergarten, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Education, PTA, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Education, Public School (1 of 2), 1997-2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Education, Public School (2 of 2), 1997-2003 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Education, Public School, 2000-2006 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Education, Public School Finance, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Education, Religion, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Education, Scholars, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Education, School Vouchers, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Education, TAAS Test, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Education, Teacher Health Insurance, 2001-2004 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Education, Teacher Retirement, 1997-2004 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Education, Teacher Work Days, 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Education, Teachers, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Education, Teachers Salary, 1997-2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Education, Textbooks, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Education, Texas Federation of Teachers, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Education, Transfers, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Education, Issue Task Force, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Eight Liners, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Elections, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Electricity (1 of 2), 1997-2005 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Electricity (2 of 2), 1997-2005 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Electronic Services, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Energy, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Ethics, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Excavation, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Family Violence, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Firearms, 1997-2007 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Firefighters, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Fireworks, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Flags, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Flags, 2007-2010 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Food Stamps, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Foster Care, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Game Fowl, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Gas, 1998-2007 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Geoscientist, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Governor George W. Bush, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Grants, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Gun Violence, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Hate Crimes Bill, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Health, Cosmetology, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Health, Counseling, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Health, Diabetes, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Health, Dental Services, 1997-2001 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Health, EMS, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Health, Handicap, 1999-2005 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Health, Health Care (1 of 2), 1997-2003 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Health, Health Care (2 of 2), 1997-2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Health, Insurance, 1997-2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Health, Medical Leave, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Health, Medicine, 1997-2005 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Health, Mental Disabilities, 1997-2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Health, Nurses, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Health, Optometry, 1997-2003 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Health, Pharmacies, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Health, Psychology, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Health, Shock Therapy, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Health, STDs, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Health, Women’s Health, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Highways and Roads, 1997-2008 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Homes, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Honorary House Page Program, 1997-2007 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Horses, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Housing, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Identity Theft, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Indian Gambling Bill, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Insurance, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Insurance Zones, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Interns, 1997-2007 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Invitations, 1997-2010 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Judicial Affairs, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Lawsuit Reform (1 of 3), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Lawsuit Reform (2 of 3), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Lawsuit Reform (3 of 3), 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - “Let Us Dream Together” Project, 2005 May (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Libraries, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Life Insurance, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Liquefied Gas, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Loans, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Loans, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Maps, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Marriage and Divorce, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Military, 1997-2003 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Newsletters, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Noise Pollution, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Nursing Homes, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Open Meetings, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Parks, 1997-2002 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Parole, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Paternity, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Patriotism, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Peace Officers, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Personal, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Pharmacies, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Pollution, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Postal Service, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Prison, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Property, 1997-2003 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Prostitution, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Public Citizen, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Public Information, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Public Utility Commission, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Radio, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Raytheon, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Real Estate, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Redistricting (1 of 5), 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 33)